YWCA of the U.S.A. Records. Record Group 6. Program: Series VII. War Work and Defense Services 324_rg6_s7
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES VII. WAR WORK AND DEFENSE SERVICES
  - Subseries C. Defense Services
    - United Service Organizations (USO)
      - YWCA Cooperation
        - Reports
          - "Digest of Information on Wartime Employment of Women" by Nora Piore, Mar 1943 (Box 734, Folder 14)
          - Executive Report-USO Division, 1941-47
            - Vol. XVI: Exhibit/Appendix J
              - Religious Material, YWCA and War Production Work, Housing (Box 734, Folder 15)
              - War Production Workers Program report by Florence Anderson (Box 735, Folder 1)
              - Play Contest, 1943-44 (Box 735, Folder 2)
            - Vol. XVII
              - Exhibit/Appendix K: Service to Negroes (Box 735, Folder 3-4)
              - Exhibit/Appendix L: Training (Box 735, Folder 5-8)
              - Exhibit/Appendix M: Budgets (Box 735, Folder 9)
          - "A Nation at Work in Wartime: a report of the wartime program of the USO Division of National Board YWCA in war production areas," n.d. (Box 735, Folder 10-11)
          - Services to Campuses by the U.S.O. Division of the National Board of the YWCA, 1941-46 (Box 735, Folder 12-15)
          - "Seven Case Studies of USO-YMCA-YWCA Joint Operations" by Margaret Williamson and Roy Sorenson, Jan 1943 (Box 735, Folder 16)
    - United Community Defense Services (UCDS)
      - General, 1952-53, n.d. (Box 735, Folder 17-19)